黑 鏡
急轉直下
原創翻譯  雙語字幕
僅供學習 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為
最新最快海外影視字幕下載
翻譯：草草
校對：草草
時間軸：倩倩  Ans  黑查
后期：吉吉  總監：草草
蕾茜
Hey, Lacie!
已打分  珍  5星
已打分  克洛伊  5星
已打分  約翰尼  5星
蕾茜
萊恩
Ryan?
Ryan!
-我剛剛拿著炸彈呢  -拜托
- I was holding a bomb! - Come on!
抱歉  伙計們
Sorry, guys.
房東今天會讓買家過來  所以
Landlord is sending buyers over today so...
穿好褲子
put your pants on.
如果我不穿  或許能嚇跑他們
Maybe if I don't, it'll scare 'em off
我們就能留下了
and we can stay here.
不行  萊恩  租約再有一個月就到期了
Not an option, Ryan. Lease is up in four weeks.
我在為你著想  我有地方去的
Hey, I'm thinking of you. I've got somewhere to go.
內特的室友去鳳凰城工作了
Nate's roommate took a job in Phoenix
我可以住他那兒
so I get his place.
-好吧  -現在是誰慢半拍了
- Okay. - Now who's the slow poke?
我午飯時要去看房
I'm... seeing some places over lunch.
回見
Catch you later.
抱歉  剛剛是我姐姐
Sorry, that was my sister.
嗯  你當然想了
Yeah. Yeah, I bet you'd love to.
茉莉茶
Jasmine tea?
已打分  薩曼  5星
已打分  基斯  5星
刷絨咖啡
And that's one Brushed Suede.
想就塊餅干嗎
You want a cookie with that?
杰克
-送你的  -那太棒了
- It's on the house. - Sounds awesome.
已打分  杰克  5星
-明天見  JJ  -回見  蕾茜
- See you tomorrow, JJ. - See you, Lacie.
我剛剛看見你兒子戴消防帽了  好可愛
Oh, I saw your boy in the fire hat just now! So cute!
基斯
是啊  他真不錯
Yeah, he's really something.
斯特芬
肖恩
約翰
凱蒂
克里斯
查理
珍
薩姆
卡爾
安迪
蕾茜·龐德  刷絨咖啡配餅干  味美如天堂
已上傳
有人為你打分了
薩姆·勃倫茲
約翰尼·詹姆斯
蕾茜
Hey, Lacie!
-貝絲  見到你真高興  -我也是
- Bets, it's great to see you! - You too.
貝絲妮
加載信息  貝絲妮·瓊斯
貝絲妮·瓊斯
薄煎餅吃薄煎餅
薄煎餅和奶油  他喜歡甜的
薄煎餅怎么樣了
How's Pancakes?
他太逗了  超逗的貓貓  最棒了
He's hilarious. Such a funny cat. Just the best.
你還在霍迪科嗎
Are you still at Hoddicker?
-嗯  挺順利的  -太好了
- Yeah. It's going pretty great. - Good to hear.
-你怎么來這兒了  -新工作  第一天
- So what brings you back here? - New job, first day.
-第一天  -在布蘭科曼-哈珀
- First day? - At Blankman-Harper.
頂樓  那...
Top floor! That's...
-祝你好運  -是啊
- Well, good luck. - I know, right?
你還喜歡待在霍迪科也很好
It's great you're still happy at Hoddicker.
-也不會待一輩子啦  -當然
- Well, maybe not forever. - No, not forever.
-但現在  -現在還湊合
- But for now... - It's OK for now.
現在很棒的  是的
It's great for now, yes. Yes, it is.
蕾茜·龐德  刷絨咖啡配餅干  味美如天堂
娜奧米·杰恩·布萊斯托
我生命中的另一個男人
蕾茜  喝杯冰沙吧
Lacie, I got you a smoothie.
每個人都有  還剩一堆呢
Got one for everyone, actually. Still a bunch of them for grabs.
切斯特
農貿市場的有機物攤位買的
They're from the organic stall at the farmers' market.
嗯  好吧
Sure. Okay.
謝謝  謝謝
Thank you. Thank you.
我們不跟切斯講話了
We're kind of not talking to Ches.
3.1  怎么回事
3.1? What happened?
他和戈登分手了
Him and Gordon split up.
可憐的切斯
Poor Ches.
不不  我們是站戈登的
No, no, no, we're all on Gordon's side.
當然了  這還用說
Sure! Obviously.
切斯在到處拍馬屁  想把分拉上去
Ches is kissing ass. Trying to scrape himself back.
當然  如果掉到2.5以下  那就
Of course, if it drops below two-five, then it's...
再見了
bye-bye.
有人為你打分了
喂
Hello?
-他們要了  -誰
- Yo, they're taking it. - Who?
房東叫來看房的那對夫婦
The couple the landlord sent over.
我聽到他們說話了
I heard them talking.
好吧
Okay.
現在我們進入光線區
So, now we move into the light space area.
很合適跟愛人度過特別時光
Ideal for special times with loved ones.
美食  佳人相伴
Great food, great company.
從你的照片流中抽樣合成的
Sampled your photo stream to make her.
發型好棒
Great hair!
在會員吧免費做的造型
Styled free of charge at the members' salon.
天吶
Oh, my God.
太逗了
It's hilarious!
你喜歡他
You like him?
-他還行  -他可不是公寓帶的
- He's okay. - He doesn't come with the apartment.
但這里有酒吧和餐廳  只限租戶
But there is a bar and restaurant on site, tenants only.
我們在浪漫際遇方面無人能比
We have unparalleled metrics on romantic geneses.
我得說  這些房子出手很快
I gotta say, these places are going like "That."
要是感興趣可別耽誤
So don't delay if you're interested.
我非常感興趣
I'm more than interested.
標準住戶最低要簽六個月合同
Standard occupancy on a minimum six-month contract,
價格...是這個數
we're talking... this much.
-交房租的頻率是  -每周
- How often are the payments? - That's weekly.
好
Okay.
-超出你預期了  -是
- A little more than expected? - Yeah.
有其他選擇
There's options.
知道我們的最優影響力項目嗎
You know our Prime Influencers Programme?
-我夠格嗎  -不  你不夠
- Do I qualify for that? - No. No, you don't.
你得在4.5左右
We'd need you around a 4.5.
4.5
4.5?
4.5分就打八折
Hit 4.5 and there's a 20% discount.
-4.5  -沒錯
- 4.5. - That's right.
鵜鶘灣
娜奧米·杰恩·布萊斯托
保羅·馬斯森
鵜鶘灣
Pelican Cove?
這是什么  優生項目嗎
What is this? A eugenics programme?
-是優質生活社區  -沒有人那么開心
- A lifestyle community. - No one is this happy.
萊恩
拿著氣球的兩歲孩子都不會這么開心
A two-year-old with a fucking balloon isn't this happy.
鵜鶘灣
這地方其實挺不錯的
It's actually a pretty cool place.
你能進得去嗎
Like you'd even qualify.
我也沒辦法  先生
There's nothing I can do, sir.
也不是沒希望  你顯然很努力
Well, it's not hopeless, you're clearly a tryer.
這是你從我身上看出來的嗎
That's the sense you get just from... me?
從你的信譽報告分析中得出的
From your rep report analytics.
如果我們仔細研究數據
If we drill down into the numbers,
你的受歡迎曲線是很不錯的
you've got a solid popularity arc here.
整體軌跡穩定  看看剛過去的24小時
Strong overall trajectory. Let's just look at the last 24 hours.
你看  就連
You see, even--
那是什么  早上8:40
What's that? 8:40 a.m.
你在社交網絡上很努力
You're working hard on your socials.
-這里有不錯的上浮  -好
- Great little uptake there. - Okay.
這里有幾個小低分  你搶車道了嗎
Couple of minor dings there. You cut someone off in traffic?
是工作上的事
Oh, just a workplace thing.
好  我們看看你的影響力球
Okay. Let's check on your sphere of influence.
我放大一下
Let me zoom out here.
外圍很棒  陌生人喜歡你  這是好事
Great peripherals. Strangers like you, that's a plus.
-內圈也不錯  這很好  -謝謝
- Healthy inner circle. It's good. - Thank you.
是有辦法的  4.5是可以達到的
There's a ways to go, but 4.5 is certainly achievable.
你覺得要多久
How long do you think?
到4.5
To hit 4.5?
除非遭遇重大挫折
Well, barring a major setback,
當眾蒙羞什么的  18個月就行
a public disgrace kind of deal, I'd say 18 months or so.
我需要更快點  快很多
Oh, I need more short term. Like... much more.
那你需要拉分
Then you'll need a boost.
-什么樣的拉分  -這個嘛
- What kind of a boost? - Well...
你大部分交際發生在內圈里
Most of your interactions are confined to your inner circle
而這些人  抱歉  他們大都是中低檔的
and they're largely, pardon the term, mid-to low-range folks.
你的外圈也是
Same with your outer circle.
你有一堆來自
You've got a ton of reciprocal
服務人員的互評五星
five stars from service industry workers,
但再就沒什么別的了
but there's not much else.
至少在我看來
At least as far as I can see.
從質量上講  你這方面需要提升
So in terms of quality, you could use a punch up right there.
最理想的是來自上等人的高分
Ideally, that's up votes from quality people.
-上等人  -大4分的
- Quality people? - High fours.
如果能打動上等人  你的曲線就會加速上揚
Impress those up-scale folks, you'll gain velocity on your arc
他們能給你拉分
and there's your boost.
-JJ  -蕾茜
- Oh, hi, JJ! - Hey, Lacie!
-基斯  你好  -蕾茜
- Keith! Hello. - Lacie!
-你今天看上去真棒  -謝謝
- You look great today. - Thank you!
門打不開  我現在2.4
Door won't open. I'm on 2.4.
抱歉  切斯  我遲了
Sorry, Ches. I'm late.
給我幾顆星吧  求你
I just need some stars, please!
我操
Fuck!
-在布蘭科曼還好嗎  -很好
- How's it going at Blankman? - Just great.
-你在那邊工作得很好吧  -謝謝
- Well, I bet you work... good there. - Thank you.
你要來個羊角面包嗎
Would you like a croissant?
咖啡廳多給了我一個
They gave me an extra at the coffee place.
-我吃過了  -好啊  好
- Oh, no, I already ate. - Okay, sure. All good. Yes.
嗯
Yeah.
我到了
Well, here's me, so...
貝絲妮·瓊斯
別用力過猛  那讓人看不起
Don't try too hard. It's impossible to respect.
大4分的人一眼就能看穿  做自己就好
High fours can smell it a mile off. Just be you.
真誠  這才是關鍵
Authentic gestures, that's the key.
-時間到了  回聊  -我想問問
- That's time up, I'll catch you later. - Oh, could I just ask--
娜奧米·杰恩·布萊斯托
保羅·馬特森
蕾茜·龐德
"老好人  破布先生"
"Good ol' Mr. Rags."
圖片已上傳
娜奧米·杰恩·布萊斯托
橄欖醬
該死
Shit!
-那是什么  -橄欖醬  來點嗎
- What the fuck is that? - Tapenade. Want some?
你是誰啊
Who even are you?
我就是想吃這個  萊恩
It's just something I wanna eat, Ryan.
天吶
Oh, my God.
-怎么了  -娜奧米
- What is it? - Naomi!
該死
Shit!
以前那個完美的娜奧米  你們有聯系
Old school, el perfecto Naomi? You guys keep in contact?
萊恩  快走  走開
Ryan, just go! Go!
天吶  娜娜  你好嗎
Oh, my God! Nay-Nay, how are you?
我正在給自己弄點點心吃
I was just fixing myself a snack.
蕾茜  見到你我太高興了
Oh, Lace, could I just say I am so happy to see your face?
-我也是  這都...  -好久沒見
- Me too. It's been... - Too long.
-太久了  -是我不好
- Way too long. - And that's my fault.
不  怪我
No, it's mine.
-事情太...  -事情太...
- Everything is just so... - Everything's just so...
瘋狂了  見到你真好
Crazy! Oh, it's so good to see you.
你發的那張破布先生的照片
When you posted that Mr. Rags photo...
是啊  破布先生
I know, Mr. Rags!
我就一定要打給你
I just had to call
跟你聊聊  因為...
and talk to you because...
好大的戒指
That's a... big ring!
恭喜  是誰...
Congratulations! Who's the, um...
保羅嗎
Paul?
他很棒  很聰明  很貼心
He is great. So smart. Just sweet.
你肯定會喜歡他的
I know you're gonna love him.
總之  大日子
So, anyways, the big day...
嗯  什么時候
Yes, when is it?
我們一個月后要在島上
So, we're getting married in a month
他家族的宅子里結婚
on his family's estate up here on the island.
是在哈尼薩克的瑪麗港外  聽說過嗎
This place outside Port Mary, Honeysuckle. You heard of it?
沒有  但是
No, but...
是座私人島嶼
Well, it's a private island.
看啊
Take a looooook!
這太...
That is...
是吧  你能來嗎
I know, right? So... can you make it?
開玩笑嗎  當然了
Are you kidding? Of course.
太棒了  我在想...
Great, cool, cos I was wondering if...
蕾茜  你覺得...
Lace, do you think...
你愿做我的伴娘嗎
Would you be my maid of honour?
真的嗎
Seriously?
天吶
Oh, my God.
你現在有很酷的朋友了  你確定嗎
I mean, you've got such cool friends now. Are you sure?
還記得嗎
Remember when we used to
我們小時候一起策劃夢想婚禮  那時才11吧
plan our dream weddings when we were, like, 11?
是啊  但我們...
I know but we haven't s--
我說不清  看到破布先生時
I don't know, just seeing Mr. Rags...
那些記憶  我一下都回憶起來了
All the memories. It just brought things home.
娜娜
Oh, Nay-Nay.
我知道我們沒能更經常聯絡  我很遺憾
I know we haven't kept in touch as much as I'd have liked
而且這也全怪我  但這是個大日子
and that is totally my fault, but this is a big day.
人生的大日子
A big life day
我希望我最久的朋友能陪伴我
and I want my oldest friend with me, my oldest friend.
我希望你陪著我
I want you by my side.
天吶  謝謝
Oh, my God. Thank you.
我要做什么...
What do I have to...
也沒什么  就是講個話
Not much to it. A speech, mainly.
講話  當然
Speech? Of course!
到時有多少人
How big's the crowd?
天吶  數百個吧
Oh, my gosh, like... hundreds!
賓客名單可長了  我這就發給你
It's a crazy guest list. I'll send it now.
保羅請了一堆人  我不想說他們是大人物
Paul's invited so many, I don't want to call them big deals,
但他們都4.7分以上
but they're all, like, 4.7 or above.
娜奧米·布萊斯托  賓客名單
娜娜  我不會讓你失望的
Nay-Nay, I will not let you down.
別太緊張  就談過去的回憶
Don't sweat too much! Just talk about old memories.
-好  -我們以前的樣子  過去的事
- Sure. - How we were, any old things.
-好  -我回頭發你點趣聞
- Gotcha. - I'll ping you some anecdotes.
-那太好了  -你裙子是幾號的
- That would be great. - And what's your dress size?
這樣吧  我給你寄件4號的
I'll tell you what, I'll just send you a four.
-太棒了  -我們有成套的伴娘裙
- Perfect. - We got matching bridesmaids dresses.
總之
Well, anyway...
愛你  小蕾
Love you, Lay.
也愛你  娜娜
You too, Nay-Nay!
再見
Bye.
鬧得什么妖啊
What was that? The F-word?
你倆還成好朋友了
You two pussy pals now?
閉嘴
Shut up.
-她一直待你很刻薄  -才沒有
- She was always mean to you. - No, she wasn't.
-她給你編了首順口溜  -那是游戲
- She had that rhyme about you. - That was a game.
-那她剪你頭發的事呢  -我讓她剪的
- What about when she cut your hair? - I asked her to.
她上了格雷戈
She fucked Greg.
她沒有上過格雷戈
She... did not fuck Greg.
她是挺性感  我承認
She looked hot. I'll give her that.
婚禮賓客名單
好
Okay.
很不錯
Impressive.
天吶  嗯  這就可以
Jesus. Yeah, that'd do it.
鵜鶘灣
Pelican Cove.
卡羅爾  我是蕾茜
Carole, it's Lacie.
我昨天去看過房  我想要了
Saw the place yesterday. I wanna take it.
太棒了
That's fantastic!
你還是個4.2  這...
Oh, I see you're still on a 4.2. Is that, um...
嗯  我在想辦法了  我這就交保證金
Yep, I'm on it, just gonna transfer the deposit now.
-好  -太棒了
- Well, okay. - Yes!
在這世上
In this world,
我們都太沉浸于自己的小世界
we're all so caught up in our own heads.
很容易忘記什么是真實的
It's easy to lose sight of what's real.
什么是重要的
What matters.
但今天我站在這里
But as I stand here today...
看到保羅給娜奧米的生活帶來的喜悅
seeing the joy Paul has brought to Naomi's life,
我知道她對我真的很重要
I know she's someone who truly matters to me.
娜娜
Nay-Nay,
小時候
the little girl who,
五歲的我們一起去藝術夏令營
when we were just five-years-old in art camp,
她看到我害怕  就來跟我說話
started talking to me because she saw I was scared.
她幫我做了破布先生
The girl who helped me make Mr. Rags.
我還留著呢
I still have him.
它就擺在我桌上
He sits on my desk and...
每天讓我回憶起娜娜
every day, he reminds me of Nay-Nay.
記起她那時對我多重要  現在也是
What she meant to me then and now.
能來到這里我非常榮幸
I am so honored to be here
我祝你們
and I wish you
擁有這愚蠢的世界所擁有的一切幸福
all the happiness this stupid world can muster.
我愛你  娜娜
I love you, Nay-Nay.
眼淚太過了嗎
Is the tear too much?
你個反社會
You fucking sociopath.
萊恩  我的車到了  太過了嗎
Ryan, my car's here. Was it too much?
眼淚  照片  破布先生
What, the tear, the photo, Mr. Rags?
我的確把它擺在桌上
I do keep him on my desk.
甜蜜是一回事  你這是糖尿病了
There's sugary and then there's fucking diabetes.
我只想在她婚禮這天哄她開心
I just wanna make her happy on her wedding day.
不得不聽你講完的4分圣人給你狂打五星
The captive audience of 4-point holies five-starring your ass off,
只是額外好處
that's just a bonus.
-娜奧米和我曾經是好閨蜜  -得了
- Naomi and I were best friends. - Come on...
我祝她好  并想盡力表達好我的祝福
I wish her well and wanna express it the best I can.
是啊  如果我講得很好
And, yeah, if I nail a speech
被幾百名上等人打了五星
and get five-starred by hundreds of primes,
那又如何  那是雙贏
so what? It's a win-win.
你要多高  4.3  4.4
What are you hoping for? Like, 4.3, 4.4?
你的游戲隊友給你高分  這是一樣的
You get points from your gaming buddies. It's the same thing.
別因為我目標遠大就噴我
Don't shit on me for aiming higher.
鵜鶘灣那么高嗎
Pelican Cove higher?
鵜鶘灣怎么了  那公寓很棒
What's wrong with Pelican Cove? They're great apartments!
那是假笑牢房
They are fake-smile jail cells.
真好  車取消了
Great. Car cancelled.
他還給了我低分
And he marked me down
這下我得再叫輛車  而且還被打了低分
so now I have to book another, and I took a ding.
-干得好  -對不起
- Great job. - I am sorry,
但我想念正常的你了
but I miss the normal you.
你執迷于此之前
Before this obsession,
我們還能好好說話呢  記得嗎
when we had conversations, remember?
我需要我的充電器
I need my charger.
這個分數的事  把你自己跟這些
This whole ranking thing, just comparing yourself to people who--
看到我的充電器了嗎
Have you seen my charger?
假裝快樂的人相比
...only pretend to be happy.
我叫你別拿的
I said don't borrow this!
娜奧米那種大4分的  肯定有自殺傾向
High fours like Naomi, I bet they're suicidal on the inside.
我的車又到了
My car is here. Again.
你的鵜鶘灣保證金  拿得回來嗎
Your Pelican Cove deposit, is it refundable?
如果這沒成功呢
Like, what if this doesn't work?
-你就不能別煩我嗎  -你是我姐姐
- Can't you just stay out of my shit? - You're my sister!
是啊  如果你真在乎  或許就會注意到
Yes! And if you cared about that, maybe you would've noticed
跟你住在一起并不是什么非常愉快的事
living with you hasn't been one big rainbow sandwich for me.
你知道我為什么從不帶人回來嗎
Do you know why I never brought any guys back here?
因為我不希望他們知道
Because I didn't want them to know
我跟一個3分二貨先生
I was sharing a skanky-ass cave
共享一間臭哄哄的公寓
with Mr. Three Point Fuck.
表演順利
Good luck with your performance!
我就來  我就來
I'm coming. I'm coming.
-天吶  -真抱歉
- Jesus Christ! - Oh, I'm so sorry.
塔瑪拉
這可好  太好了
That's great. Just great.
視頻通話
娜娜
Nay-Nay!
蕾茜  就問問你
Hey, Lace! Just checking in.
我正在趕往機場
I'm on my way to the airport right now.
好啊  你準備好來參加彩排晚宴了吧
Okay, cool, and you're all good for the rehearsal dinner?
是的  要飛一小時左右吧
Oh, yeah. The flight's, what, an hour?
餐廳看上去很不錯
That restaurant looks so cool.
收到裙子了吧
And you got the dress okay?
在我箱子里
In my case.
粉色我喜歡
I love the pink.
講話的最新一稿很棒
So the latest draft of the speech is great.
手寫真酷
Going handwritten's so cool.
我一看掃描件  天吶  都淚涌了
Those scans of the page, my God, I welled up just at that.
-謝謝  -就一點
- Oh, thank you! - Just one thought.
關于你患有飲食失調時我幫了你的事
That whole bit where I help you with the eating disorder thing...
-你覺得有點...  -透露隱私了
- You think that's a little... - A little over-sharing, yeah.
你說得太對了  我刪掉
You're so right. It's gone.
好  那幾小時后見了
Okay. Cool. Well, I'll see you in a few hours!
*我明天就結婚了*
*I'm getting married tomorrow*
你的小費  謝謝
And here's your tip. Thank you.
拜托
Oh, come on.
請注意
May I have your attention, please...
-你好嗎  -我很好
- Hi there, how are you doing? - I am wonderful.
對不起  這趟航班被取消了
I am so sorry, that flight is cancelled.
-不不  -另一邊出現了客戶事故
- No. No, no, no. - Customer incident at the other end.
但...下一班飛機是什么時候
But... So when is the next flight?
都滿員了
Yeah, they're all kind of full.
這是我幾周前訂好的  是我最好朋友的婚禮
I booked this weeks ago. It's my best friend's wedding.
-對不起  -我必須趕過去
- I'm sorry. - I have to get there. I have to.
好吧  我想想辦法
Okay-- let's see what we can do.
謝謝  太感謝了
Thank you. Thank you so much.
一架今晚出發的航班還有個保留位置
I see there's one standby seat on another plane leaving tonight.
是為我們最優航班項目會員預留的
That's reserved for members of our Prime Flight Programme.
你得超過4.2分才行
You gotta be a 4.2 or over to qualify.
我就是4.2
Oh, I'm... I'm a 4.2.
恐怕你是4.183
I'm afraid you're actually a 4.183.
這不能怪我
Well, that's not my fault.
有個女人拉了我的分  你不能...
Some woman dinged me down in the... Can't you just--
對不起  分數不對  我訂不到機票
I'm sorry, it won't let me book it without the correct ranking.
-但就差一點啊  -我也沒辦法
- But it's so close. - There's just nothing I can do.
老天爺  肯定有辦法吧
Christ, I mean, surely.
我需要請您注意用語
I'm gonna have to ask you to moderate your language there.
對不起  我...
Sorry. It's just...
我是伴娘  我不能錯過婚禮
I'm maid of honour. I cannot miss this wedding.
那真是太抱歉了
And I am so sorry about that.
-你能打給你的上級嗎  -不行
- Can you call the supervisor? - I cannot do that.
-你就打給上級吧  -我不能那么做
- Can you just call the supervisor? - I cannot do that.
-他媽的找上級來  -好吧  這是臟話
- Call the fucking supervisor! - Okay, that's profanity.
-我們對臟話是零容忍的  -對不起
- We're zero tolerance on profanity. - I'm sorry. It's just--
-我得接待下位客戶了  -不要
- I have to serve the next customer. - No, no, no, no.
-請你讓開  女士  -他媽的幫幫我
- Can you step away, ma'am? - God, just fucking help me!
真對不起
I'm so sorry.
-我已經叫保安了  -不  別那么做
- I've called security. - Oh, no, no, no. Please don't do that.
我給你打5星  5星
I'm, uh... five-starring you. Five stars.
-怎么了  漢娜  -恐嚇和說臟話
- What's the issue here, Hannah? - Intimidation and profanity.
-不  我沒有恐嚇她  -別說話  女士
- Oh, no, no. I was not intimidating. - Don't speak, ma'am.
-我就是想  -女士
- I was just trying to-- - Ma'am.
好吧  為了恢復平靜
Okay. So, in order to restore calm,
我要使用作為機場保安的權利
I'm invoking my authority as airport security
給你扣1分  作為懲罰
to dock you one full ranking point as a punitive measure.
-這只是臨時措施  -不
- This is a temporary measure. - No!
你的分數24小時后會恢復正常
Your score reverts to normal in 24 hours.
-不行  我現在就需要分數  -在此期間
- No, no, no. But I need it now. - During this period,
所有低分將被乘二
all down votes are subject to a times two multiplier.
乘二
Times two?
我們建議你在此期間避免負面反饋
We recommend you avoid negative feedback at this time.
我現在低分翻倍了
I'm on double damage?
請立刻離開機場
Please, remove yourself from the airport immediately.
好吧  由于你的分數
Okay, well, due to your ranking...
快速通道  4分以上
你好  恰克  名字真棒
Hi there. Chuck! Great name.
-謝謝  -希望你今晚愉快
- Thank you. - Hope you're having a great night.
-挺好的  -我需要輛車
- It's pretty good. - So I need a car.
-有具體想要的車嗎  -隨便
- You got a vehicle in mind? - Anything, really.
由于你現在的分數
Well, due to your current ranking,
只可以選擇特惠車
you're restricted to our super saver fleet.
-嗯  好吧  -巡游2號
- Yep. That's... Yeah. - I-Cruiser 2?
還有2號的
They still have the 2?
天吶
Oh, God.
拜托
Oh, come on.
第一時間下載無刪減美劇  必須登錄字幕組網站
該死
Damn it!
更好更快的原創翻譯 雙語字幕
小時候
The little girl,
五歲的我們一起去藝術夏令營
who when we were both five years old in art camp,
她看到我害怕  就來跟我說話
started talking to me because she saw I was scared.
她幫我做了破布先生
The girl who helped me make Mr. Rags...
眼淚  觀眾歡呼
Teardrop. Crowd goes wild.
你可以的
You can do this.
對不起  我在趕去了
Sorry, okay, I swear I'm on my way.
你還有多遠
How far away are you?
還挺遠  我錯過了航班
Quite a ways. I missed my flight.
-什么  -不是錯過了  但...
- What? - Well, not missed it but...
你趕不上彩排晚宴了
So you're not gonna make the rehearsal dinner?
-嗯  -蕾茜
- No. - Lacie!
對不起  我...
I am so sorry. It's been...
我租了車  我在開車
I got a rental car. I'm driving.
開車  那要九小時才能到
Driving? That's like nine hours.
我開得很快
I'm making good time,
我會開通宵  就當公路旅行了
gonna go through the night, make a road trip out of it.
你沒事吧
Is everything okay?
如果有問題我可以找人替你
I can find a replacement if something's wrong.
不不  我會趕去的
No. No. No. I'll be there.
我以破布先生起誓
I swear on Mr. Rags.
路上小心
Okay, just drive safe!
當然  我...
You bet. I'll just--
給娜奧米打分
已打分  娜奧米  5星
拜托
Come on.
別這樣
Please.
好
Okay.
你想干什么
What do you want?
充電
該死
Oh, shit.
對不起
Sorry.
你的充電器跟我的車不配套
Your charger doesn't fit my car.
-這種如今不多見了  -是租的
- Don't see those around much these days. - It's a rental.
我們的充電器是Q2Z的  你那是K1的
Ours chargers are Q2Z, yours one's a K1.
他們沒給你適配器嗎
They didn't give you an adapter?
沒有  你有嗎
No. Do you have one?
這里沒有  去問問看
Not in here. Ask around.
還是謝謝了  你幫了大忙
Thanks, anyway. You're super helpful.
兩星
Two stars?!
Two stars?
不是什么有意義的偶遇
Wasn't a meaningful encounter.
先生  打擾
Sir, excuse me.
打擾  抱歉
Excuse me, sorry.
你有K1適配器嗎
Do you have a K1 adapter, by any chance?
女士  你呢  K1適配器
Ma'am, how about you, a K1 adapter,
你行李箱里有嗎
perhaps, in the trunk of your car?
好吧
Sure.
太好了
Great.
女士  你有K1適配器嗎
Oh, ma'am, hi. Do you have a K1 adapter?
我租了輛車
I have a rental car. It's...
蕾茜
停下  我們載她一程吧
Slow down. Let's give her a ride.
蕾茜
她才2.8
She's, like, 2.8.
拜托
Come on!
我什么都沒做
I didn't even do anything!
蘇珊
你似乎需要搭車
You look like you need a ride.
其實  不用了
Actually, I'm okay.
看來需要啊
Don't look it.
來吧  我不咬人
Come on. I don't bite.
路瑟  咖啡太太  赤紅  威士忌  你自便
Luther, Mrs. Coffee, reds, whiskey. Help yourself.
不用  謝謝
I'm okay. Thanks.
你去哪
Where are you headed?
盡量靠近瑪麗港就行
Just as close as you can get to Port Mary would be great.
在翻我的信息找危險跡象嗎
Checking my feed for danger signs?
常有人這樣
I get it a lot.
1.4的人肯定是反社會的瘋子  是吧
1.4 gotta be an antisocial maniac, right?
-你似乎  -挺正常
- You seem... - Normal?
-嗯  -謝謝
- Yeah. - Thank you.
還是很費了一番力的  你是怎么了
It took some effort. What happened to you?
你2.8  你看上去可不像2.8的
I mean, you're a 2.8, but you don't look 2.8.
那是...暫時的
That's not-- This is temporary.
我回扭轉過來的
I'm gonna turn it around.
我要去參加婚禮
I'm going to a wedding.
-我是伴娘  -不錯啊
- Maid of honour. - Nice.
想聽聽我的講話嗎
Wanna hear my speech?
不想
No.
你怎么落到2.8的
So how come you're a 2.8?
我因為在機場大吼被扣分了
Well, I got marked down at the airport for yelling,
他們還給我開了低分翻倍
and they put me on double damage.
-感覺怎么樣  -很糟
- How did it feel? - Awful.
我是說大吼
I meant the yelling.
我不知道  我當時生著氣
I don't know. I was mad.
瞧我落得什么下場
Look at where it got me.
但只要我趕到婚禮  講了話
But as long as I get to the wedding, do the speech,
他們不會在意我是2.8的
they'll overlook the 2.8.
我是新娘的朋友
I'm with the bride.
如果我做得好  他們都是大4分的
And if I do well, well, they're all high fours
會迅速拉高我的分數
so that velocitates my arc.
等罰分解除
And once they lift the point penalty,
我的平均分就會上去
well, my average goes way up,
那就沒事了
and, yeah, it's gonna be okay.
天吶  你讓我想起了自己
God, you remind me of me.
不是現在
Not now.
我曾經是4.6分
I was, uh... 4.6 once.
-4.6  -以前視此為生命
- 4.6? - Used to live for it.
我付出了那么多努力
All the work I put in...
八年前  湯姆  我丈夫得了癌癥
Eight years ago, Tom, my husband, got cancer.
胰腺癌  非常討厭
It was pancreatic. It was a real bitch.
癥狀出現得很晚
The symptoms showed up late.
我很遺憾
I'm so sorry.
你并不認識我  所以不會怎么遺憾
You don't know me so you're not really sorry.
你主要是覺得尷尬
You're just mainly awkward
因為我突然對你談起了癌癥
cos I have sprung some cancer talk at you.
總之  我給每個醫生  護士
Anyway, I five-starred every doctor,
大4分的會診醫生都打了五星
every nurse, every high-four consultant that we had.
非常感謝
Thank you so much.
但癌癥才不在乎  它還是繼續擴散
The cancer didn't give a shit. It just kept growing.
幾個月后
A couple of months in,
我們聽說了一個實驗治療
we heard about this experimental treatment.
非常昂貴  而且不好進
It was very expensive. It was very exclusive.
為了幫他爭取位置我想盡了辦法
I did everything I could to get him a spot there.
湯姆是4.3
Tom was a 4.3.
他們把他的位置給了個4.4的
They gave his bed to a 4.4.
所以他死后  我想  去他的
So when he died I thought, fuck it.
我開始隨時隨心所欲地說話
I started saying what I wanted, when I wanted.
就那么沖口而出
Just drop it out there.
人們并不總喜歡我這樣
People don't always like that.
你一開始這么做  分數嗖嗖下滑
It is incredible how fast you slip off the ladder
簡直難以置信
when you start doing that.
原來很多我的朋友并不喜歡誠實
It turned out a lot of my friends didn't care for honesty.
他們對我就好像我在他們早餐桌上拉了屎
Treated me like I had taken a shit at their breakfast table.
但是  那感覺真妙
But, Jesus Christ, it felt good.
擺脫那些混蛋
Shedding those fuckers.
就像脫掉一雙擠腳的鞋
It was like taking off tight shoes.
-或許你也該試試  -得了
- Maybe you should try it? - Oh, come on.
為什么不呢
Why not?
我不能就踢掉鞋子到處走
I can't just kick off my shoes and walk the earth or whatever.
-你不試怎么知道  -那是...
- You won't know unless you try. - Oh, that's just...
你生命中曾有一些
Look, you had something with your life,
真實  美好的東西  你全部失去了
real things, good things, and you lost it all,
我很遺憾
and I'm sorry.
你現在沒什么可失去的了
So now you've got nothing left to lose.
但我都沒有值得失去的東西呢
But I don't even have the something worth losing, not yet.
我還在為那個奮斗
You know, I mean, I'm still fighting for that.
"那個"是什么
And what is "that"?
我不知道  讓我知足的東西
I don't know. Enough to be content?
能環顧四周  然后想
Like, to look around and think,
我混得不錯
well, I guess I'm okay.
能夠自如呼吸  不會覺得...
Just to be able to breathe out, not feeling like... like...
就是...
Like just...
那還差得很遠呢
And that is way off, like, way, way off.
我做到那個境界之前
And until I get there,
我還得遵守分數游戲的規則
I have to play the numbers game.
我們都得  我們就活在這種世界里
We all do, that's what we're in.
這世界就他媽是這個規矩
That's how the fucking world works.
或許你不記得了
Look, maybe you don't remember,
你年紀太大了  不懂了
you know, you're just too old to get it.
我不是那個意思
I do not mean that how it sounds.
別擔心  我不會給你低分的
Don't worry. I'm not voting you down.
親愛的
Sweetheart.
幾點了
What time is it?
我之后要向東了
I'm heading east from here
你得再搭輛車了
so I think you need to get yourself another ride.
-我們在哪  -離瑪麗港還有30英里
- Where are we? - About 30 miles from Port Mary.
這里有很多大巴站  你應該沒問題了
A lot of buses stop here so you should be fine.
-謝謝你  -講話順利
- Well, thank you. - Good luck with your speech.
我給你放了點東西進去
I put a little something in there for you.
-是嗎  -緊急出口
- You did? - Emergency escape hatch!
再見
Bye.
在這世上  我們都太沉浸于
In this world, we're all so caught up...
自己的小世界
...in our own dramas.
-爸爸還說  -很容易忘記什么是重要的
- So, Dad was like... - It's easy to forget what matters.
他沒聽過那個節目
He'd never even heard of the show.
我說  "你沒聽過《靜海》"
I'm like, "You never heard of Sea of Tranquillity?"
那是排名第一的科幻片
Like, the number-one sci-fi fantasy,
他說  "什么鬼"  隨便了
and he's all like, "What the fuck?" Whatever!
我覺得我對這紫色過敏
I think I'm allergic to this purple.
我就說  "我要去瑪麗港的靜海大會
So I'm like, "Well, I'm going to Tranquillity Con in Port Mary.
所以才扮成了達斯特中尉"
That's why I'm dressed like Lieutenant Duster."
他說  "瑪麗港那么老遠"
He's all like, "Uh... Port Mary is frickin' miles away."
然后給了我1星   謝了  老爸
He one-stars me. Like, thanks, Dad.
搜索結果
-回見  -好
- See you back on there. - Okay.
你們要去靜海大會嗎
Are you guys headed to Tranquillity Con?
-你也喜歡《靜海》  -當然
- You're into Sea of Tranquillity? - Totally.
我打算去的
I was all set to go.
我朋友已經到了
My friend, who is there already,
我的服裝在她那兒  但我的車壞了
has my costume, but my car broke down.
房車里還有地方
Well, there's some space in the RV.
-你是個靜粉吧  -什么
- You're a Trank head, huh? - Sorry?
靜粉  《靜海》粉絲
Trank head. Sea of Tranquillity fan?
是啊  我們那邊叫海粉的
Oh, yeah. We say Tranksters where I'm from.
-你最喜歡的人物是誰  -達斯特中尉吧
- Who's your favourite character? - Gotta be Lieutenant Duster.
-她太棒了  -她
- She's awesome. - She?
他  我口誤
He! I misspoke.
達斯特中尉沒有固定性別
Lieutenant Duster has no fixed gender.
是啊  所以才不容易記住
I know, and that's why it's so hard to remember, right?
失陪  我得接一下
Excuse me. Gotta get this.
我朋友  在大會上的
My friend, at the convention.
娜娜
Hi, Nay!
天吶  昨天晚上真夠嗆
So, oh, my God, insane night,
但我就到了
but I am so close now.
別來了
Don't come.
什么  不不  我就差一小時的路了
What? No. No. I'm, like, an hour away.
別來了  我不要你來
Don't come. I don't want you here.
我不知道你是怎么回事
I don't know what is up with you,
但我不能讓2.6的人出現在我的婚禮上
but I cannot have a 2.6 at my wedding.
不  那是暫時的  暫時的
Oh, no, that's temporary! That's temporary.
婚禮就在今天了
Well, the wedding's today so...
-這并不能改變什么  -蕾茜
- But it doesn't change anything. - Lacie...
-我還是可以講話的  -蕾茜
- I can still do the same speech. - Lacie...
-還有破布先生  -不行
- And there's Mr. Rags! - No!
但是  你邀請我了
But... But you invited me.
你看過賓客名單了  他們都4.5以上
You've seen the guest list. They are all, like, 4.5 or above.
你個2.6會格格不入
They are going to freak at a 2.6,
我不要那樣的負面影響
and I am not taking that kind of damage,
再說  我都六個月沒低于過4.7了
plus I haven't dipped under a 4.7 in, like, six months.
你說你希望你最久的朋友去的
You said you wanted your oldest friend.
我叫你來講話時  你是4.2
When I asked you to speak, you were a 4.2, okay?
我們進行過各種模擬  在這種規模的集會上
And the authenticity of a vintage bond low four
跟小4分的陳年友誼的真實性
at a gathering of this calibre
會產生非常好的效果
played fantastically on all the stimulations we ran.
據預測至少能提高.2分
Forecast was a prestige bounce of .2 minimum.
但現在你低于3了  對不起
But now you're a sub three. Sorry.
這就太不討喜了
That just puts the stink on things a little too much.
對我們不會有利
That just plays badly for us.
你只在乎分數嗎
So it was just about numbers for you?
少來了  我們都一樣
Oh, cut the shit! It was numbers for both of us.
你想要上等人的高分  別否認了
You wanted those primo votes, don't deny it.
你憑自己又得不到
It's not like you could get them on your own.
我們就別自欺欺人了
Let's not kid ourselves.
我會得到高分的
Oh, I'm... I'm getting those votes.
怎么  你打算就跑過來逼人喜歡你嗎
What? You're just gonna roll up here and make people like you?
-沒錯  我要做我的講話  -你不能
- That's right. I'm doing my speech. - No, you're not.
我就要
Yes, I am.
等他們聽了  會給我打高分的
And they are gonna vote me through the roof when they hear it.
會把眼淚流干
Weep their fucking eyes out!
回家去吧
Go home!
喂
Hello?
操
Fuck!
我從沒看過你們的破電視劇
I have never seen your stupid fucking show.
希望它被砍
Hope they cancel it!
我需要搭車
I need a ride!
操
Fuck!
天吶
Jesus!
-能借你的摩托嗎  -什么
- Can I borrow your bike? - What?
能借你的摩托嗎
Can I borrow your bike?
你  娜奧米·杰恩·布萊斯托
Do you, Naomi Jayne Blestow,
是否愿與此人結為夫婦
take this man to be your husband,
與他一起共筑婚姻
to live together with him in the covenant of marriage?
愛他  撫慰他
To love him, comfort him,
尊敬他  守護他
honour and keep him,
不論疾病或健康
in sickness and in health...
不再眷顧其他人  忠于他
and forsaking all others, be faithful unto him...
歡迎來到哈妮薩克
最低限入分數3.8分  違者止步
敬我的伴郎  安東尼  為他鼓掌
To my best mate, Anthony. Let's hear it for him.
你一直在我左右
You've been there from day one.
我愛你  伙計  我感激你
I love you, man. I appreciate you.
按你的標準  講話還是很逗的
Hilarious speech, by the way. By your standards.
他還剩幾顆子彈呢  天吶
He's still got a few bullets left. Oh, man.
天吶
Oh, gosh, well, um...
該死
Shit!
我們要感謝太多人  美麗的伴娘們
We have so many people to thank. Our beautiful bridesmaids.
但當然
But, of course,
我最真摯的感激  最溫暖的謝意
my most heartfelt thanks, my warmest thanks,
是給我最好的朋友  我的情人
are to someone who's my best friend, my lover
如今  我很榮幸地說
and now, I'm honoured to say,
她也是我妻子
my wife.
娜奧米
Naomi!
Naomi.
一二三  娜奧米
One, two, three! Naomi!
A隊
The A Team!
我好愛你  親愛的
I love you so much, darl.
來吧
Come on.
恭喜  先生
Congratulations, sir.
-謝謝  -不  謝謝你
- Thank you. - No, thank you.
過來
Get over here!
給我過來
Get your ass over here.
過來  小子
Get in here, big boy.
你真美
You're beautiful!
來  來個5星  選得好
Yeah! Gimme five! Good choice!
你應得的  應得的
You fucking earned it, man. You fucking earned it.
大家好
Everybody, hello!
-天吶  -我愛你
- Oh, my God. - I love you.
大家能安靜一下嗎
Can everyone be quiet for a moment?
謝謝
Thank you.
-趕走她  -那會很不好看的
- Get rid of her. - That would play awful.
她才1.1
She's a fucking 1.1.
如果你不認識我...
Now for those of you who don't know me,
那包括你們所有人
which is... all of you...
我叫蕾茜·龐德
my name is Lacie Pound
信不信由你  我是娜奧米最久的朋友之一
and, believe it or not, I am one of Naomi's oldest friends.
娜娜
Hi, Nay-Nay!
也很高興認識你  保羅
It's great to meet you too, Paul.
聽說了你不少好事
I've heard a lot about you.
他可是個大人物  那個保羅
He's a pretty big deal, that Paul.
大人物啊
Pretty big deal.
他會自己做橄欖醬  沒錯
He makes his own tapenade! Yeah.
總之
Anyway, um... I...
我這輩子一直敬仰娜奧米
have looked up to Naomi pretty much my entire life.
我們五歲時相識
We met when we were five years old,
一直到十幾歲都是朋友
and right up through to our teenage years,
是一對兒好姐妹
we made quite the pair.
我們會聊各種閨蜜間的話題
We'd talk about all the things girls talk about,
男孩  頭發  商品
you know, boys, hair, products,
還有男孩
more boys.
我有時會想擴展一下話題
I mean, I tried sometimes to expand our range a little
聊聊氣候變化
and talk about climate change,
但她覺得那無聊  所以
but she found that kind of boring so...
去啊
Go on.
她可能是對的  去他的地球  是吧
She was probably right. I mean, fuck the planet, right?
謝謝  來吧  讓氣氛活躍一點
Yes, thank you! Come on. Let's have a little fun here.
去他的地球
You know, fuck the planet!
Fuck the planet!
已打分  蕾茜  1星
總之
Anyway...
我這輩子
I... looked up
一直敬仰娜奧米
to Naomi pretty much my entire life,
所以她一直在俯視我
which meant she was looking down on me.
但總是面帶微笑的
Always with a smile though.
高中時  她是讓我哭泣的肩膀
In high school, she was my shoulder to cry on.
她似乎很喜歡那樣
She seemed to enjoy that.
我總沒有男人緣
Guys and me never worked out.
他們一看到娜奧米就...
They'd see Naomi and just...
我就沒戲了
You know, that was it.
她屁股緊翹
She had this tight ass,
就像拳頭
like two fists.
我就...
I was all like...
我...
I was like...
穿過高中的走廊
through the hallways in high school.
她一直陪著我
And she was there for me.
替我抓著頭發
Holding my hair back...
讓我跪在馬桶前吐
as I knelt, vomiting, in front of the crapper.
謝謝了  娜奧米
Thank you for that, Naomi.
我一直希望自己是你
I always wished I was you.
而且
And...
這才是你留了我那么久的原因吧
I guess that's why you kept me around so long?
直到你找到了新工作
Until you got your new job
和厲害的新朋友
and your fancy new friends.
還有那個
And that...
他媽的
...fucking...
混球
jackhole!
你不需要我了  你可能又找了個新我
And you didn't need me. You probably got another me.
大概有個
Guess there's some other
新可憐人被你個妖女盯上了
"Yeth Beth" you moved on to like a succubus.
我這就說到破布先生  好嗎  天吶
I'm getting to Mr. Rags, okay? Jesus!
別過來
Stay back.
別他媽過來  要不我殺了它
Stay the fuck back! I'll kill him!
我會砍下它的頭  塞進我屁股里
I'll cut his head off and stick it up my ass!
時間就要到了
Time's nearly up!
-冷靜下來  -我
- Calm down. - I...
我想說  在這世上
I just wanted to say, in this world
我們都太沉浸于自己的破事
we all so caught up in our own shit,
-不要忘記什么才是重要的  -沒事的
- let's not forget what matters. - It's okay. It's okay.
幸福
Happiness,
他媽的保羅和娜奧米
fucking Paul and Naomi, and she's...
她
She...
她上了格雷戈
She fucked Greg!
我知道她上過他
I know she did.
-我知道你干了  -沒有
- I know you did. - No...
別想否認
Don't even try to deny--
小時候
The little girl who,
五歲的我們一起去藝術夏令營
when we were just five-years-old in art camp,
她看到我害怕  就來跟我說話
started talking to me because she saw I was scared
她幫我做了破布先生
and helped me make Mr. Rags.
它讓我回憶起你  記起你那時對我多重要
He reminds me of you and what you meant to me then!
我很榮幸能來這里見證這破玩意
And I'm so honoured to be here to see this shit!
我愛你  娜娜
I love you, Nay-Nay!
我一直都愛你
I've always loved you!
我愛你
I love you!
你他媽看什么呢
What the fuck are you looking at?
我也在想呢
Just what I was wondering.
好吧
Well...
別
Don't!
別什么  別想嗎
Don't? Don't wonder?
不想這世界會很沉悶
It would be a dull world without wonder.
我才不在乎你的世界
I don't give a shit about your world.
我不喜歡你的胸罩
I don't like your brassiere.
我不喜歡你的小胡子
I don't like your moustache.
我不喜歡你的氣場
I don't like your aura.
-我的氣場  -嗯
- My aura? - Yeah.
我不喜歡你的...
I don't like your...
頭  你整個頭我都覺得可笑
head. Your entire head is just ridiculous to me.
是嗎
Really?
你就像
You look like
酗酒的前天氣預報員
an alcoholic former weatherman.
你就像只迷途羔羊
You sound like a lost little lamb
剛得知了這世上沒有圣誕老人
that just got told there's no Santa Claus.
你媽媽是干了哪個卡通人物
What sort of cartoon character did your mum have to fuck
才懷上你的
to brew you up in the womb?
至少我看上去像生出來的
At least I look like I was born,
不是被地下實驗室里
not shit out by some
哪只被受折磨的奶牛怪拉出來的
tormented cow creature in an underground lab.
你被從那個實驗室里丟了出來
You got tossed out of that lab.
-是嗎  -是啊  沖出來的
- Oh, yeah? - Oh, yeah, flushed out.
沖進了垃圾堆
In the trash!
-你的臉是他媽...  -什么
- Your face is a fucking... - Fucking.
他媽的
Fucking
生物撞車
biological car crash
畢加索都覺得辣眼睛
that made Picasso screw his eyes up and say,
說  "這是什么玩意嘛"
"Well, that just don't make sense."
-你是個他媽的混蛋  -去你媽
- You're a fucking asshole. - Fuck you!
-下周三去你媽  -圣誕節去你媽
- Fuck you next Wednesday. - Fuck you for Christmas!
-去你媽  -去你媽
- Fuck you! - Fuck you!